David Samoylov

+7 (707) 000-76-27 | eaaanesmlv@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/aaaenesmlv

Авоит

A Software Engineer with 5 years of extensive experience in designing, developing, and maintaining robust backend applications. Enthusiastic about enhancing my core skills while also keeping up with the latest industry trends and best practices.

EXPERIENCE

Kaspersky Moscow, Russia *Research Developer* Apr. 2021 – Aug. 2023

- Developed and maintained a development environment for anti-malware records, complemented by an integrated version control system and support for distributed compilation across multiple platforms.
- Implemented a command-line tool to facilitate the creation of Visual Studio projects and the generation of C++ DLLs for debugging purposes, which significantly improved malware analysts workflow.
- Created a log analysis tool that helped to identify recurring problems and establish connections between seemingly unrelated issues, which enhanced team troubleshooting capabilities.
- Collaborated with a team to employ an application metric collection system, integrating it with Grafana for dashboards and alerts, resulting in reduced incident response time from hours to minutes.
- · Accomplished the migration of the anti-malware records from Perforce to Git.
- · Developed a plugin that performs static code analysis of a domain-specific programming language.
- · Migrated a project CI pipeline from TeamCity to Azure DevOps.

KomdiagnostikaSoftware Engineer

Orenburg, Russia

Aug. 2018 – Apr. 2021

- Developed and maintained a software solution for vibration-based condition monitoring, automated spectrum analysis and predictive maintenance.
- · Implemented a database disk usage prediction system, enhancing monitoring capabilities.
- Participated in application profiling and optimization and accelerated spectrum harmonic analysis algorithm up to four times.
- Engineered a portable device for vibration analysis, including designing the UI layout, developing the application architecture, and implementing the software for data collection and analysis.

EDUCATION

Orenburg State University

Master of Science in Mathematics and Computer Science Sep. 2016 – Jun. 2018

Orenburg State University

Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering

Orenburg, Russia Sep. 2012 – Jun. 2016

Orenburg, Russia

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: C#, PowerShell, Python, SQL. Familiar with C/C++ **Frameworks**: .NET, .NET Framework, WPF. Familiar with ASP.NET Core **Developer Tools**: Git, TFS, TeamCity, Azure DevOps, Elasticsearch, Grafana **Libraries**: NUnit, xUnit, Serilog, NLog,

Benchmark.NET, Dapper